<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Astro Blogger</title>
    <description><![CDATA[ An Astro theme for blogging with index page pagination and full RSS. ]]></description>
    <link>http://localhost:3000/</link>

    <item>
      <title>People Are Not Thumb Drives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/thumb-drives</link>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/thumb-drives</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[ You can't transfer your memories to a baby, and even if you could, the baby would not be you.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You can&#39;t transfer your memories to a baby, and even if you could, the baby would not be you.[^1]</p>
<blockquote>
<p>John: Trying to transfer your memories to a baby, that doesn&#39;t make any sense, and it doesn&#39;t change the baby into you, even if you could do it.</p>
<p>Jason: So premise rejected.</p>
<p>John: Mmm-hmmm.</p>
<p>Jason: Sorry, Vitor, I tried.</p>
<p>John: People are not thumb drives.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>[^1]: A footnote test</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/the-hole</link>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/the-hole</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[ A hole is not a tube.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:23:38 PDT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A hole is not a tube.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The hole is the top surface, the hole is not the interior, right?</p>
<p>Like if you&#39;re inside a cave, right, the cave is the inside part, but you could go through a hole to get into the cave.</p>
</blockquote>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Blooming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/no-blooming</link>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/no-blooming</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[ John buys a new TV and his family is not impressed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:21:00 PDT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John buys a new TV and his family is not impressed.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>So anyway, I give the whole experience a big thumbs up. I am much more excited and impressed by this television than anyone else in my family, I can tell you that. They don&#39;t care.</p>
<p>I showed them the footage of the honey dripping onto the thing on a black background... how are you not impressed by that? There&#39;s no blooming, it&#39;s HDR, every pixel is individually lit up!</p>
</blockquote>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro-level</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/micro-level</link>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/micro-level</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[ Nothing in John's house is level.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:23 PDT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nothing in John&#39;s house is level.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I do like this stand, it&#39;s served me well. It&#39;s got glass shelves, holds everything up pretty well. I did micro-level it because of course nothing in my house is level.</p>
<p>It&#39;s mostly level. If you put a level on it and look at the little bubble, it&#39;s between the two lines. But is it in the middle between the two lines? Almost!</p>
</blockquote>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Birds Are Out Of Control</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/birds</link>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/birds</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[ Birds poop on John and steal sandwiches out of his hand while he's eating them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Birds poop on John and steal sandwiches out of his hand while he&#39;s eating them.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>While this is happening, I&#39;m eating my sandwich. We make our own little sandwiches and bring them to the beach. I&#39;m eating my sandwich, and a bird comes from behind me, in the air, and takes a bite of my sandwich that is in my hand, that I am in the process of eating. He didn&#39;t get the sandwich because I grabbed it as they went away, but he took a bite out of it. And of course now I have to throw out that whole sandwich because it&#39;s got bird bite on it, alright? I don&#39;t want the bird slobber. It&#39;s in my hand, right?</p>
<p>That happened to I think one other person so the new move was while we&#39;re eating lunch, hold your food close to your chest and be aware that the nearest bird may be behind you. We&#39;re watching in front of us, we&#39;re watching all these birds, watching them or whatever, I thought I was covered.</p>
<p>And there was an umbrella too, the thing flew like under the umbrella, over my shoulder, over the back of the seat, and you know, while still flying went aah-chomp! and tried to grab the sandwich out of my hand.</p>
<p>These birds are out of control. I don&#39;t know what has gotten into them. They&#39;re not afraid anymore, and they&#39;re poopin&#39; on us, and they&#39;re stealing our food out of our hands while we eat it.</p>
</blockquote>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
  </rss>
  